<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Combat Bionics (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CombatBionics</packageId>
  <author>Freefolk</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/CombatBionics</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Freefolks mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2469409798

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://discord.gg/h5TY6DA][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/CombatBionics][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Can't you carry more guns with only two hands? Would you like to live your own Mandalorian fantasy? Enter Combat bionics.

[h1]Content[/h1]

Combat bionics adds mainly two bionics to the vanilla game, with increasing content depending on other mods, namely VE series and Royalty. Descriptions follow:

[b]Minigun Arm:[/b] An advanced artifical arm, with a built-in retractable minigun. While providing combat advantage, it matches the performance of a biological arm.

[b]Swarm Wrist:[/b] An advanced artifical hand, with a built-in single use missile swarm. While providing combat advantage, it is better than a biological hand in almost every way.

[b]Jump Pack Spine:[/b] An advanced artifical spine, with a built-in jump pack system. While providing combat utility, it matches the performance of a biological spine. Requires Royalty.

[b]Flamer Wrist:[/b] An advanced artifical arm, with a built-in flamethrower. While providing combat advantage, it is better than a biological arm in almost every way. Requires VWE - Heavy Weapons.

[b]Laser Wrist:[/b] An advanced artifical hand, with a built-in laser shooter. While providing combat advantage, it is better than a biological hand in almost every way. Requires VWE - Laser.

[b]Tesla Wrist:[/b] An advanced artifical hand, with a built-in electric weapon. While providing combat advantage, it is better than a biological hand in almost every way. Requires VWE - Laser.

[b]Tear Gas Arm:[/b] An advanced artifical arm, with a built-in tear gas canister launcher. While providing combat advantage, it is better than a biological arm in almost every way. Requires VWE - Non-Lethal.

[h1]FAQ[/h1]

Q: How do I reload the swarm wrist?
A: Pawns automatically reload their bionics when you undraft them, as a job. Or you can force them to reload by hovering over the gizmo to see what's needed to reload, then right clicking the appropriate ammunition to give the reload order.

[b]Freefolk Modding Team[/b]

Credits: Freefolk Modding Team. Special thanks to legodude17.
Rimworld is owned by Tynan Sylvester.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Log Uploader[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list] 

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/3260597442][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/CombatBionics?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url] | tags:  combat enhancements</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.6.1</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>